export  const Quizdata=[{
    question:"It was Sunday on Jan 1, 2006. What was the day of the week Jan 1, 2010?",
    options:["Sunday","Saturday","Friday","Wednesday"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"What was the day of the week on 28th May, 2006?",
    options:["Thrusday","Friday","Saturday","Sunday"],
    answer:4
},{
    question:"What was the day of the week on 17th June, 1998?",
    options:["Monday","Tuesday","Wednesday","Thursday"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"What is the value of Pi to four individual decimal places?",
    options:["3.1416","32.1416","3.51416","3.2"],
    answer:1
},{
    question:"What does 6 raise to the power of 0 equal?",
    options:["6","1" ,"0 ","36"   ],
    answer:2
},{
    question:"Solve the following equation: -15 + (-5x)=0. ",
    options:["1","3","0","-3"],
    answer:4
},{
    question:"A car is traveling at the rate of 75 kilometers per hour. How many meters is the car traveling in one minute?",
    options:["1250 m/min","250 m/min","1856 m/min","522 m/min"],
    answer:1
},{
    question:"How many hours are there in a year (rounded to the nearest hour)?",
    options:["4596 hours","8760 hours","2556 hours","2159 hours"],
    answer:2
},{
    question:" Which number is best represented in binary as 100? ",
    options:["1","6","4","2"],
    answer:3
},{
    question:"60 Times of 8 Equals to",
    options:["481","480" ,"490","482"],
    answer:2
}];

export const tru=[true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true,true];